Guide to the Alan Pryce-Jones Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1857-2000; Series IV; 7.5; (18 boxes)
  - FINANCIAL PAPERS
    - Insurance
      - The Yorkshire Insurance Company Limited, 1952-60 (Box 59, Folder 2262)
      - Miscellaneous Auto Insurance, 1948-92, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2263)
      - Miscellaneous Life and Health Insurance, 1960-87, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2264)
      - Miscellaneous Home and Property Insurance, 1943-61, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2265)
    - Residence and Property Files
      Arranged chronologically by
      dates of residence or ownership
      - England
        - 4 York Gate, London, 1942-50, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2266)
        - The Bothy, Somerhill, Tonbridge, 1948-66 (Box 59, Folder 2267)
          See also: Oversize, Box Bsd, folder 2436
        - 27 Cavendish Close, London, 1951-54 (Box 59, Folder 2268)
        - A.9-A.10 Albany, London: Adams, C. H., Secretary, 1957-64 (Box 59, Folder 2269)
        - A.9-A.10 Albany, London: Fladgate & Co., 1954-64 (Box 59, Folder 2270)
        - A.9-A.10 Albany: general, 1956-63 (Box 59, Folder 2271)
      - New York City
        - 19 East 55th Street, 1960-66 (Box 59, Folder 2272)
        - 134 West 58th Street, Apartment 803, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 2273)
        - 1 Beekman Place, Apartment 2B, 1971, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2274)
        - 9 East 74th Street, Apartment 5A, 1986-89 (Box 59, Folder 2275)
      - Newport, Rhode Island
        See also: Kirby, Inc., Box 58, Folder 2255
        - 46 & 50 John Street and 4 Martin Street, 1962-94, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2276-2277)
        - 220-222 Spring Street: Carey, Richmond & Viking/Walter Jenkins Whitley, 1971-95 (Box 59, Folder 2278)
        - 220-222 Spring Street: Hall, D'Addario & Machtley/Joseph M. Hall, 1971-84 (Box 59, Folder 2279)
        - 220-222 Spring Street: general, 1973-83 (Box 59, Folder 2280)
        - 1 Martin Street, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 2281)
    - Medical Records
      - Medical reports, prescriptions and receipts, 1948-94, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2282-2283)
        Includes correspondence from
        doctors
    - Bills and Receipts
      - A. Pinou & Son, 1964-92 (Box 60, Folder 2284)
      - American Airlines, 1988-94, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2285)
      - American Express, 1978-93 (Box 60, Folder 2286)
      - Andrews Express & Storage Warehouse, 1971-75 (Box 60, Folder 2287)
      - Antiques and restoration, 1959-86 (Box 60, Folder 2288)
      - Army & Navy Stores, 1952-95 (Box 60, Folder 2289)
      - Art galleries, 1962-77 (Box 60, Folder 2290)
      - AT&T, 1985-89 (Box 60, Folder 2291)
      - Auctions, 1957-61, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2292)
      - Automobiles, 1952-90, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2293)
      - Bookshops, stationers, and magazine subscriptions, 1958-94, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2294)
      - Charles Hamilton Galleries, Inc., 1982, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2295)
      - Charities, 1980-90 (Box 60, Folder 2296)
      - Cleaners, 1958-87, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2297)
      - Crutch Brothers Limited, 1957-64 (Box 60, Folder 2298)
      - Diners Club, 1996, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2299)
      - Food and drink, 1958-61, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2300)
      - The Georgian Group, 1950-92 (Box 60, Folder 2301)
      - Home and garden, 1937-76, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2302)
      - Hotels, 1932-83, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2303)
      - Little Sisters of the Poor, 1979-91, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2304)
      - Martin's Removals & Storage, 1966-78, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2305)
      - Mastercard/Visa, general, 1976-95 (Box 60, Folder 2306)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, N.Y.), 1985-88 (Box 60, Folder 2307)
      - Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.), 1989-95, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2308)
      - Office equipment and electronics, 1960-90, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2309)
      - Parking violations, 1959-79 (Box 60, Folder 2310)
      - Photography, 1958-86 (Box 60, Folder 2311)
      - Postal services, 1953-61, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2312)
      - Sears, Roebuck and Co., 1979-93 (Box 60, Folder 2313)
      - Shipping and customs, 1960-84, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2314)
      - Spouting Rock Beach Association, 1967-94 (Box 60, Folder 2315)
      - Travel, 1938-86, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2316)
      - Utilities, 1957-61 (Box 60, Folder 2317)
      - Other receipts, 1956-91 (Box 60, Folder 2318)
      - Hudson, Larry, miscellaneous receipts and statements, 1973-94 (Box 60, Folder 2319)
  - OFFICIAL DOCUMENTS AND RELATED MATERIAL
    - Birth certificate, certified copies of 1908 document, 1972-74 (Box 61, Folder 2320)
    - Eton College reports to Henry Morris Pryce-Jones regarding APJ, 1922-27 (Box 61, Folder 2321-2325)
      Includes letters from Aymer W.
      Whitworth to HMPJ; accompanied
      by [certificate?] for Maths
      from St. Peter's School,
      possibly relating to Adrian
      Pryce-Jones [?]
      See also: Oversize, Box 65, Folder 2437
    - Passports, 1924-83 (Box 61, Folder 2326-2329)
    - Marriage announcement for APJ and Baroness Thérèse Fould-Springer, 1934 Dec (Box 61, Folder 2330)
      Manuscript press release
      by Vere Pryce-Jones and
      clippings
    - Driver's licenses, 1937-74 (Box 61, Folder 2331-2332)
    - Cabinet du Préfet des Alpes Maritimes, pass to travel from Nice to London, 1939 Aug 25 (Box 61, Folder 2333)
    - Will, holograph statement, 1939 Oct 4 (Box 61, Folder 2334)
    - Curriculum vita, holograph draft, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 2335)
    - Military papers: "Officer's Release Book," and various passes, 1945-46, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 2336)
    - Certificates of vaccination and related forms, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 2337)
    - Certificate of Eligibility for Exchange Visitor Status, and extension, [U.S.] Department of State, 1960-61 (Box 61, Folder 2338)
    - Identification card and waiver, U. S. Department of Justice, Immigration & Naturalization Service, 1961 Apr 2, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 2339)
    - Estate plan, jointly with Mary Jean Kempner Pryce-Jones, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 2340)
    - Will, typescript photocopy, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 2341)
    - Will, typescript photocopy, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 2342)
    - Debrett's Handbook entry form, filled out by APJ, 1986 Jan 31 (Box 61, Folder 2343)
    - Will, typescript photocopy, 1987 Dec 2 (Box 61, Folder 2344)
      For 1992 Will,
      See: Financial Papers, Bankers Trust, Box 57, Folder 2205-2207
    - Memorial service program for APJ, 2000 Jun 11 (Box 61, Folder 2345)
  - PROFESSIONAL (NON-LITERARY) WORK
    - Ford Foundation
      - "The Ford Foundation Program in Humanities and the Arts," printed pamphlet, 1959 Feb (Box 61, Folder 2346)
      - "Interim Report no. 1," to the Ford Foundation by APJ, typescript carbon, 1960 Sep 26 (Box 61, Folder 2347)
      - "Ford Foundation Conference of Visual Artists," program and holograph notes, 1961 Jun (Box 61, Folder 2348)
      - Conference on "The Public Understanding of the Role of Science in Society," program, 1962 March (Box 61, Folder 2349)
      - "Ford Foundation Conference on Architects and Designers," program and holograph notes, 1962 Jun (Box 61, Folder 2350)
    - Liberal Party
      - Candidacy for Louth Division, Lincolnshire: speech draft, newsletters, and advertising material, 1939 (Box 61, Folder 2351)
    - MI14
      - "The Reply to English Propaganda," by Reich Minister Dr. [Joseph] Goebbels, printed pamphlet, 1939 Jul 14 (Box 61, Folder 2352)
        With envelope addressed to
        Mrs. Claude Beddington
      - Intelligence and related material, 1940, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 2353)
        Includes anonymous tip from
        France; "Most Secret" extract of
        German report about St. Vincent
        Troubridge; and teletype print-
        out of exchange between Eric
        Birley and another operator
        See also: Oversize, Box 65, folder 2438
  - OTHER PAPERS
    - Address Books
      - Address books (14), 1934-[90s] (Box 62, Folder 2354-2361)
      - Addresses and phone numbers, loose manuscript notes (Box 63, Folder 2362)
      - Business cards and calling cards (Box 63, Folder 2363)
    - Lists of Possessions
      - "Wedding Presents," bound volume with additional lists laid in, [1934-35] (Box 63, Folder 2364)
      - Lists of objects for homes in Vienna and London, by Thérèse Pryce-Jones, [1934-39] (Box 63, Folder 2365)
      - Lists of objects and clothing in storage, by Doris Gibbins Mercer, 1964, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2366)
    - Memberships and Affiliations
      - Club membership lists, general, 1954-89 (Box 63, Folder 2367)
      - Literary societies and clubs, membership cards and related material, 1949-82, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2368)
      - Theater societies, clubs, and subscriptions, membership cards and related material, 1949-61 (Box 63, Folder 2369)
      - Other membership cards and related material, 1939-90, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2370)
      - Social and Court event programs, menus, gift subscriptions, and invitations, 1939-85 (Box 63, Folder 2371)
    - Drawings
      - Portrait of unidentified subject, Pen and ink, by Evan Morgan, 1930 Sep 17 (Box 63, Folder 2372)
      - Portrait of Thérèse Fould-Springer Pryce-Jones, pencil
        See: Series III, Photographs, Box 46, folder 2057
      - Set design [?] by ["Maria?"] showing small domed building and trees, watercolor and pencil (Box 63, Folder 2373)
      - "J.T. 5 months," outline of infant's foot and hand, pencil (Box 63, Folder 2374)
        [Jessica Thérèse Pryce-Jones?]
      - Drawing of flowers, pencil and watercolor, unfinished (Box 63, Folder 2375)
      - Drawing of half-timbered buildings, watercolor and pencil (Box 63, Folder 2376)
      - Typewriter drawing of palm tree and eye (Box 63, Folder 2377)
    - Clippings and Printed Ephemera
      - APJ in the press
        See also: Series II, Scrapbooks, Boxes 66-68, folders 2429-2433
        - General clippings, 1933-55 (Box 63, Folder 2378)
        - General clippings, 1962-80 (Box 63, Folder 2379-2380)
        - Cover story: "Alan Pryce-Jones / Newport's Intellectual Standard Bearer," Newport This Week, 1984 Jan 5 (Box 63, Folder 2381)
        - Cover story: Times Literary Supplement article on Horst featuring his photo of APJ, 1985 Mar 8 (Box 63, Folder 2382)
        - Feature: "Newport's Mr. Jones and his 3 tiny Homes," Providence Sunday Journal, 1985 Nov 3 (Box 63, Folder 2383)
      - Other Subjects
        - General clippings, 1938-93, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2384-2385)
        - Obituary clippings and memorial service cards and programs, 1946-95 (Box 64, Folder 2386-2387)
          Includes family and friends
        - Parish news bulletins, 1945-87 (Box 64, Folder 2388)
          Accompanied by miscellaneous
          religous pamphlets and poems,
          including "Aimée Semple McPherson
          Campaign / under the auspices of
          the Elim Foursquare Gospel
          Alliance [...] / Hymn Book"
        - Promotional material for books and lectures by various writers, 1944-82, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2389)
          Removed from APJ's books
        - Sales catalogs and advertising brochures, various products, 1979-88, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2390)
        - Theater programs, museum guides, and music recording liner notes, 1957-89, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2391)
        - Travel itineraries and brochures, 1969-81, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2392)
        - Warranties, owner's manuals, and certificates of authenticity, 1956-92, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2393)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Curriculum vitae and resumés of others, 1959-94 (Box 64, Folder 2394)
      - "Private Sitting with Mr. C. R. Dell [...] Main Subject: Mediumship," typescript carbon transcript, 1948 Aug 5 (Box 64, Folder 2395)
      - "Quinta da Capela, Sintra, Portugal," house rental prospectus, by Daniel K. Thorne, typescript photocopy, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2396)
      - Franklin, Benjamin, typescript copy of letter to "My Dear Friend," 1745 Jun 15, concerning older women (Box 64, Folder 2397)
      - Letter from "a German Village School-master" to "an English Lady," typescript copy with introductory note, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2398)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Dawnay family
      - Dawnay, Lewis, manuscript notes about, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2399)
        Accompanied by photograph
        of a drawing/photograph
        of Dawnay, dated April 1910
    - Grey family
      - Grey family genealogies, manuscript and typescript (Box 64, Folder 2400)
      - Grey, Albert Henry George Grey, 4th Earl, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2401)
        Typescript copy of letter from
        Grey to unidentified recipient,
        1913 Oct 19, and clippings
      - Grey, Caroline Farquhar, passport for her, her daughter, governess, and manservant Thomas [Wyatt?], 1857 Jul 4
      - Grey, Mary Elizabeth Ponsonby Grey, Countess, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2402)
        Manuscript and typescript copies
        of excerpt of 1835 letter to the
        Duchesse de Tallyrand, and
        manuscript and typescript copies
        of an excerpt from Thackeray's
        "Sketches in London"
      - St. Albans, Sybil Mary Grey de Vere Beauclerk, Duchess of, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2403)
        Charles Grey to [Caroline Farquhar
        Grey?] about his daughter, 1862
        Dec 28, and typescript carbon copy
        of letter from the Duchess of St.
        Albans to Lady Shannon, 1871 Aug 9
    - Pryce-Jones family
      - David Pryce-Jones
        - Birth certificate, 1936 Feb 15 (Box 64, Folder 2404)
        - Eton College reports to APJ, 1952-54 (Box 64, Folder 2405)
        - Clippings, 1976-88 (Box 64, Folder 2406)
          Review of DPJ's Unity Mitford and engagement announcement
          for his daughter Jessica
      - Henry Morris and Vere Dawnay Pryce-Jones
        - Wedding invitation, program and clippings, 1905 Aug (Box 64, Folder 2407)
        - Printed lists and clipping showing HMPJ's rank in His Majesty's Body Guard, 1938-52 (Box 64, Folder 2408)
        - Certificates of burial of ashes, 1952, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 2409)
      - Mary Jean Kempner Pryce-Jones
        - Press release, memorial service program draft, and obituary clipping, 1969 Sep (Box 64, Folder 2410)
      - Sir Pryce Pryce-Jones
        - Memorial pamphlet and biographical article, 1920-79, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2411)
      - Thérèse Pryce-Jones
        - Letter to miscarried child, [ca. 1951] (Box 64, Folder 2412)
    - Springer/Fould-Springer family
      - Booklet about Vogelsang-Heim, formerly the Springer family home in Meidling, Austria, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2413)
        Includes chapter on the family,
        including APJ, as well as the
        history of the house (a.k.a.
        Springervilla or Springer-
        Schloss); accompanied by
        related clipping
- Oversize, 4.5; (4 boxes)
  - "1549 Prayer Book," proof (in Series II) (Box 65, Folder 2414)
  - "Alan Pryce-Jones leaving for America [...]" galley proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2415)
  - "The American Migraine," galley proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2416)
  - "Christmas Disaster," galley proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2417)
  - "Do Males Dress to Attract Females? or to Annoy Their Elders, or to Band?" proof (in Series II), 1965 Dec 15 (Box 65, Folder 2418)
  - "The Glories of Glass," proof (in Series II), 1963 (Box 65, Folder 2419)
  - "The Good Life: Virtue in Our Time," proof (in Series II), [1953] (Box 65, Folder 2420)
  - "Newport, Rhode Island," galley proof (in Series II), 1973 Mar 5 (Box 65, Folder 2421)
  - "Nothing Can Erase Christmas," galley proof (in Series II), 1964 (Box 65, Folder 2422)
  - "The Rococo Spirit," galley] proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2423)
  - Single reviews, various publications, proofs (in Series II), 1956-57, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2424)
  - Reviews possibly by APJ (in Series II), 1964-73, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2425)
  - Graves, Robert, obituary, proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2426)
  - Sitwell, Osbert, obituary, galley proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2427)
  - Squire, John Collings, Sir, obituary [?], proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2428)
  - Scrapbook (in Series II), 1931-34 (Box 66, Folder 2429)
  - Scrapbook (in Series II), 1931-47 (Box 66, Folder 2430)
  - Scrapbook (in Series II), 1933-39 (Box 67, Folder 2431)
  - Scrapbook (in Series II), 1951-52 (Box 67, Folder 2432)
  - Scrapbook (in Series II), 1961-63 (Box 68, Folder 2433)
  - Photograph Album (in Series III), 1908-[ca. 1925] (Box 68, Folder 2434)
  - London Life Association Ltd., insurance policy for David Pryce-Jones (in Series IV), 1936 Aug 5 (Box 65, Folder 2435)
  - "Alterations to the Bothy, Somerhill," diazo print (in Series IV), n.d. (Box Bsd, folder 2436)
  - Eton "School Certificate Examination" results, printed sheet (in Series IV), 1925 Dec (Box 65, Folder 2437)
  - Teletype exchange between Eric Birley and another operator (in Series IV) (Box 65, Folder 2438)
  - Passport for Caroline Grey, her daughter, and servants (in Series IV), 1857 Jul 4 (Box 65, Folder 2439)
- Restricted Fragile Papers
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 5 (Box 69, Folder 2440)
  - Box 1, folder 49 (Box 69, Folder 2441)
  - Box 1, folder 58 (Box 69, Folder 2442)
  - Box 4, folder 178 (Box 69, Folder 2443)
  - Box 6, folder 207 (Box 69, Folder 2444)
  - Box 7, folder 234 (Box 69, Folder 2445)
  - Box 8, folder 324 (Box 69, Folder 2446)
  - Box 10, folder 440 (Box 69, Folder 2447)
  - Box 11, folder 551 (Box 69, Folder 2448)
  - Box 13, folder 719 (Box 69, Folder 2449)
  - Box 14, folder 727 (Box 69, Folder 2450)
  - Box 14, folder 728 (Box 69, Folder 2451)
  - Box 15, folder 784 (Box 69, Folder 2452)
  - Box 16, folder 868 (Box 69, Folder 2453)
  - Box 21, folder 1001 (Box 69, Folder 2454)
  - Box 24, folder 1176 (Box 69, Folder 2455)
  - Box 24, folder 1202 (Box 69, Folder 2456)
  - Box 24, folder 1222 (Box 69, Folder 2457)
  - Box 25, folder 1287 (Box 69, Folder 2458)
  - Box 26, folder 1331 (Box 69, Folder 2459)
  - Box 27, folder 1410 (Box 69, Folder 2460)
  - Box 33, folder 1560 (Box 69, Folder 2461)
  - Box 33, folder 1562 (Box 69, Folder 2462)
  - Box 33, folder 1563 (Box 69, Folder 2463)
  - Box 33, folder 1567 (Box 69, Folder 2464)
  - Box 33, folder 1580 (Box 69, Folder 2465)
  - Box 33, folder 1598 (Box 69, Folder 2466)
  - Box 34, folder 1628 (Box 69, Folder 2467)
  - Box 34, folder 1646 (Box 69, Folder 2468)
  - Box 34, folder 1651 (Box 69, Folder 2469)
  - Box 35, folder 1662 (Box 69, Folder 2470)
  - Box 35, folder 1673 (Box 69, Folder 2471)
  - Box 35, folder 1675 (Box 69, Folder 2472)
  - Box 35, folder 1678 (Box 69, Folder 2473)
  - Box 35, folder 1682 (Box 69, Folder 2474)
  - Box 35, folder 1722 (Box 69, Folder 2475)
  - Box 35, folder 1725 (Box 69, Folder 2476)
  - Box 36, folder 1734 (Box 69, Folder 2477)
  - Box 36, folder 1735 (Box 69, Folder 2478)
  - Box 36, folder 1736 (Box 69, Folder 2479)
  - Box 36, folder 1737 (Box 69, Folder 2480)
  - Box 36, folder 1738 (Box 69, Folder 2481)
  - Box 36, folder 1749 (Box 69, Folder 2482)
  - Box 37, folder 1750 (Box 69, Folder 2483)
  - Box 37, folder 1752 (Box 69, Folder 2484)
  - Box 37, folder 1756 (Box 69, Folder 2485)
  - Box 37, folder 1765 (Box 69, Folder 2486)
  - Box 37, folder 1766 (Box 69, Folder 2487)
  - Box 38, folder 1769 (Box 69, Folder 2488)
  - Box 38, folder 1770 (Box 70, Folder 2489)
  - Box 38, folder 1775 (Box 70, Folder 2490)
  - Box 38, folder 1788 (Box 70, Folder 2491)
  - Box 38, folder 1797 (Box 70, Folder 2492)
  - Box 38, folder 1798 (Box 70, Folder 2493)
  - Box 38, folder 1802 (Box 70, Folder 2494)
  - Box 39, folder 1820 (Box 70, Folder 2495)
  - Box 40, folder 1831 (Box 70, Folder 2496)
  - Box 40, folder 1837 (Box 70, Folder 2497)
  - Box 51, folder 2117 (Box 70, Folder 2498)
  - Box 57, folder 2214 (Box 70, Folder 2499)
  - Box 57, folder 2222 (Box 70, Folder 2500)
  - Box 58, folder 2231 (Box 70, Folder 2501)
  - Box 59, folder 2278 (Box 70, Folder 2502)
  - Box 59, folder 2279 (Box 70, Folder 2503)
  - Box 59, folder 2283 (Box 70, Folder 2504)
  - Box 60, folder 2287 (Box 70, Folder 2505)
  - Box 61, folder 2351 (Box 70, Folder 2506)
  - Box 64, folder 2386 (Box 70, Folder 2507)
  - Box 64, folder 2387 (Box 70, Folder 2508)
  - Box 64, folder 2394 (Box 70, Folder 2509)
  - Box 64, folder 2408 (Box 70, Folder 2510)
  - Box 64, folder 2410 (Box 70, Folder 2511)
  - Box 64, folder 2413 (Box 70, Folder 2512)
  - Box 45, folder 2037 (Box cs, Folder 2556)
  - Box 45, folder 2048 (Box cs, Folder 2557)
  - Box 46, folder 2064 (Box cs, Folder 2558)
  - Box 46, folder 2063 (Box cs, Folder 2559)
- Restricted Fragile Oversize
  - Box 9, folder 420 (Box 71, Folder 2513)
  - Box 29, folder 1486 (Box 71, Folder 2514)
  - Box 31, folder 1509 (Box 71, Folder 2515)
  - Box 31, folder 1512 (Box 71, Folder 2516)
  - Box 33, folder 1565 (Box 71, Folder 2517)
  - Box 33, folder 1571 (Box 71, Folder 2518)
  - Box 33, folder 1572 (Box 71, Folder 2519)
  - Box 34, folder 1608 (Box 71, Folder 2520)
  - Box 34, folder 1609 (Box 71, Folder 2521)
  - Box 35, folder 1681 (Box 71, Folder 2522)
  - Box 35, folder 1684 (Box 71, Folder 2523)
  - Box 36, folder 1739 (Box 71, Folder 2524)
  - Box 36, folder 1741 (Box 71, Folder 2525)
  - Box 36, folder 1744 (Box 71, Folder 2526)
  - Box 36, folder 1745 (Box 71, Folder 2527)
  - Box 36, folder 1747 (Box 71, Folder 2528)
  - Box 36, folder 1748 (Box 71, Folder 2529)
  - Box 37, folder 1751 (Box 71, Folder 2530)
  - Box 37, folder 1753 (Box 71, Folder 2531)
  - Box 37, folder 1754 (Box 71, Folder 2532)
  - Box 37, folder 1757 (Box 71, Folder 2533)
  - Box 38, folder 1767 (Box 71, Folder 2534)
  - Box 38, folder 1768 (Box 71, Folder 2535)
  - Box 38, folder 1786 (Box 71, Folder 2536)
  - Box 38, folder 1787 (Box 71, Folder 2537)
  - Box 40, folder 1834 (Box 71, Folder 2538)
  - Box 41, folder 1936 (Box 71, Folder 2539)
  - Box 44, folder 2013 (Box 71, Folder 2540)
  - Box 63, folder 2378 (Box 71, Folder 2541)
  - Box 63, folder 2379 (Box 71, Folder 2542)
  - Box 63, folder 2380 (Box 71, Folder 2543)
  - Box 63, folder 2381 (Box 71, Folder 2544)
  - Box 63, folder 2382 (Box 71, Folder 2545)
  - Box 63, folder 2383 (Box 71, Folder 2546)
  - Box 63, folder 2384 (Box 71, Folder 2547)
  - Box 63, folder 2385 (Box 71, Folder 2548)
  - Box 64, folder 2401 (Box 71, Folder 2549)
  - Box 64, folder 2406 (Box 71, Folder 2550)
  - Box 64, folder 2407 (Box 71, Folder 2551)
  - Box 65, folder 2414 (Box 71, Folder 2552)
  - Box 65, folder 2419 (Box 71, Folder 2553)
  - Box 65, folder 2422 (Box 71, Folder 2554)
  - Box 65, folder 2427 (Box 71, Folder 2555)